Name: Tinelle Springer

Date of Birth: 10TH April 1993 Contact Number: 18683880770

Address: #13 Springer Lane, Pentecostal Road, Tunapuna

National Insurance Number: 03 165 5512 Identification Number: 19930410049 Email Address: njaleekorri22@gmail.com

Professional Profile

Possess excellent time management and adaptation skills, and responsible with an attention to detail. Organized and takes initiative to be a leader, logical, precise and analytical, able to work unsupervised or in a team environment. Highly personable Customer Service Representative with over two (2) years' experience. Proficient with Microsoft Office System.

Work Experiences

• B-Mobile Flagship Outlet- Secure Mobile.

CSR and Cashier. May 2011 to June 2011

C&V Café. November 2010 to March 2011.

Store Manager.

• **GT Jewellers Trincity Mall**. 5th – 28th August 2014

Cashier and CSR.

Marquis Restaurant and Bar

Waitress and Cashier.

• Digicel Head Office. July 29th 2015 - April 17th 2016

Digicel Play as an Inbound agent.

• iQor. October 24th - December 15th, 2016

Jr. Agent

Educational Background

El Dorado West Secondary School

Start: 2005 Finish: 2010

Subjects Attained (General)

English- Grade 2 Food and Nutrition- Grade 2 Home Management- Grade 3

Continued Studies

Metal Industry Company Limited (M.I.C)

Course: Food Preparation and Culinary Arts

September 2011 to May 2013 Certificate upon completion

MultiSector Training Programme (MuST)

Course: Hospitality and Tourism (Receptionist, Guest Services, Housekeeping and Food Prep.

Training Sites: House of Chan, The University Inn

September 2013 to February 2014

CVQ upon completion

Hobbies

Cooking Hairdressing

References

Name: Michele White

Company: Tunapuna Boys R.C School

Position: Teacher

Contact Number: 1868-742-7390

Name: Risa-Ann Lawrence-Baptiste

Company: Digicel

Position: Customer Care Agent **Contact Number**: 1868-307-7008